In 2025, Prudential Vietnam continues to
mark its journey of community service with
outstanding activities.
Firstly, it's a place for sharing
love and support, aiming to ignite hope and
empower vulnerable communities
, especially those
severely affected by natural disasters and floods.   The
series of activities included providing
essential supplies, donating learning spaces
and necessary equipment, and making
many other meaningful contributions.  Facing
successive storms and floods
in 2025, Prudential is providing
VND 1 billion to help mitigate the consequences of storms and
floods in the northern provinces
and VND 600 million in the central provinces
through the Vietnam Children's Protection Fund
.  With the desire to bring more
joy and laughter to children,
Prudential is organizing a series of Christmas events
as part of its celebrations marking
26 years of Prudential's presence in
Vietnam.
This year's program saw the
participation of hundreds of employees and
consultants, helping Prudential spread
the spirit of sharing from within the company
to the community.
Not stopping at volunteer activities
in Vietnam, Prudential and the
Prudence Foundation have collaborated to bring the
Cru volunteer program across
borders to Van Chan commune, Lao Cai province.
The program brings together volunteers
in 14 different markets.
The total value of the support, amounting to billions of VND,
directly benefits thousands of
students and households through
infrastructure improvements in numerous schools
and residential areas.
The highlight was a heartwarming meal
and cultural exchange event for hundreds of
Prudential students, teachers, and coaches.  In parallel, Prudential
also has long-term projects that create
sustainable value for the community.  The
proactive healthcare ecosystem, launched in
December 2024, continues to deliver
tangible impacts by equipping
students,
teachers, and parents with knowledge and skills in healthcare.   The "
Safe Journey to School" program marks 5
years of implementation, contributing to raising
traffic safety awareness for future generations
.
In 2025, Prudential will implement nine
community support projects with a total budget of
over 28 billion VND, benefiting
nearly 100,000 people nationwide
through reputable partners such as the
Vietnam Children's Protection Fund, the
Red Cross, and several other partners.
Prudential's persistent efforts in
2025 were recognized when it
was honored as one of the
businesses recognized by the community at the
Signature Time CSR 2025 program.
Prudential will continue to work together to connect
resources, implement
sustainable community initiatives, and spread
social responsibility.  Let's work together with Prudential to
fulfill our mission of bringing complete peace of mind
to every Vietnamese family.   lower.